<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
  <title>Heather Renkel Blog</title>
  <link>https://heatherrenkel.github.io/blog_home.html</link>
  <description>[CDATA[  ]]</description> 
<pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 16:51:24 +0000</pubDate>

  <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 18:37:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>

  <language>en-us</language>

    <item>
    <title>Dr. Michael Levitt Excess Death Estimates</title>
    <link>https://heatherrenkel.github.io/excess_death_age_location.html/xml/xml_rss.asp</link>
    <description>[CDATA[Dr. Michael Levitt excess death for the Covid pandemic 2020 2021 022 Israel US UK Chile Florida California New York New York City France Italy Germany Sweden Norway Iceland Denmark Netherlands Belgium Spain Portugal]]</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 9 Mar 2022 18:37:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>

    <category>science Statistics Excess Death Covid</category>
      <language>en-us</language>

    <copyright></copyright>
  </item>

  ////////

 <item>
    <title>What is Excess Death</title>
    <link>https://heatherrenkel.github.io/blog/what_is_excess_death.html/xml/xml_rss.asp</link>
    <description>CDATA[Since the start the Covid-19 pandemic, the scope of it’s severity often has been expressed in terms of Covid cases. The Covid death toll is then also based on this; its Covid cases who died that are listed as Covid deaths. But relying on who is recorded as a Covid case is not the best way to determine the impact of Covid, there is another way of measuring deaths that can be done by finding excess deaths. What is excess death, why it is important, and several prominent methods of measuring excess death in during the Covid pandemic are examined.]]</description>
    <category>article</category>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17??? Mar 2021 18:37:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
 </item>

 <item>
    <title>The Noise from Brazil</title>
    <link>https://heatherrenkel.github.io/blog/noise_from_Brazil.html/xml/xml_rss.asp</link>
    <description>[CDATA[Ariel Karlinsky is an economist and statistician who has become well known during the Covid pandemic for his excess death estimates. Even if his name is not familiar, his data surely will be, since it is used as a reference by many official sources.  Unfortunately his death estimates that so many rely on are corrupt. In addition to the many other errors in his excess death methods the method he uses for Brazil raises current mortality there by 8% above the official listed counts, artificially making excess death permanent and a return to normal impossible.]]</description>
    <category>blog article Covid science</category>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17??? Mar 2021 18:37:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
        <author>Heather Renkel</author>
    <copyright></copyright>
  </item>

 <item>
    <title>Report Number Nine</title>
    <link>https://heatherrenkel.github.io/blog/report_9.html/xml/xml_rss.asp</link> ????
    <description>[CDATA[Years after the Covid pandemic started we are still both mired in mitigations and suffering from their effects. Report number nine was the work of Neil Ferguson and the Imperial College of London that started the panic and brought about lockdowns for most of the world. Just how corrupt the report was is unbelievable and it's lack of scientific integrity is worth examining in detail]]</description>
    <category>article</category>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2022 18:37:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Corona Chronicles A Journal of Discovery</title>
    <link>https://heatherrenkel.github.io/blog/Corona_Chronicles-A_Personal_Journal_of_Discovery.html/xml/xml_rss.asp</link>
    <description>[CDATA[The Wall Street Journal proclaims in its ads that it's integrity and trustworthiness as a source will then be transferred to the reader, yet they consider their sources trustworthy only as long as they like the message. At the beginning of April 2020 Dr. Michael Levitt was asked by The Wall Street Journal to write an editorial piece about his his research on the Covid-19, but then immediately rejected it without explaination]]</description>
    <category></category>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <copyright>Dr. Michael Levitt</copyright>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Science Based Censorship Censoring Science During Covid</title>
    <link>https://heatherrenkel.github.io/blog/censored_sciencebasedmedicine.html/xml/xml_rss.asp</link>
    <description>[CDATA[Censorship of scientists and citizens during the Covid pandemic. It's not only experts that have been censored during the Covid crisis, it is also anyone who attempts to promote or defend them. On November 25, 2021 I attempted to submit a comment on the website sciencebasedmedicine.org in response to the article posted there on November 19, 2021 by Jonathan Howard, Contrarian Doctors: The Pandemic is Over, Again which attacked many scientists who have opposed various aspects of the response to the Covid and produced scientific evidence that ran contrary to claims made by other scientists or the media. My comment was immeditely removed, and the appeal I made to reconsider my post was rejected]]</description>
    <category>article</category>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <author>Dr. Michael Levitt</author>
  </item>

 <item>
    <title>Covid Moratlity Compared to Other Mortality During the Covid Pandemic</title>
    <link>https://heatherrenkel.github.io/blog.html/xml/xml_rss.asp</link> ????
    <description>Covid Moratlity Compared to All Cause Mortality During the Covid Pandemic from March 2020 to July 2021 by Age Groups</description>
    <category>article</category>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 2 Sep 2021 18:37:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <language>en-us</language>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Secrets of the Diamond Princess</title>
    <link>https://heatherrenkel.github.io/index.html/xml/xml_rss.asp</link>
    <description>[CDATA[A one year anniversary commemoration of Dr. Michael Levitt's analysis of the cruise ship the Diamond Princess, which was an early and very accurate assessment of the Covid pandemic and the amount of deaths we could expect from it. R naught, asymptomatics, and other aspects of the outbreak are examined]]</description>
     <category>article</category>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 18:37:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
  </item>

   <item>
    <title>Behind the Diamond Princess</title>
   <link>https://heatherrenkel.github.io/step_by_step.html/xml/xml_rss.asp</link>
    <description>A detailed in-depth look at Dr. Michael Levitt's analysis of the cruise ship the Diamond Princess, which refutes the Imperial College of London and Sir David Spiegalhalter's assertations of massive deaths</description>
     <category>article</category>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 18:37:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
  </item>

 </channel>
</rss>
